The inevitable has vettabled.
ICE just took the life of a woman in her car driving away.
You asked about a shooting that we just had in Minneapolis, Minnesota.
It was an act of domestic terrorism.
What happened was our ICE officers were out in enforcement action.
They got stuck in the snow because of the adverse weather that is in Minneapolis.
They were attempting to push out their vehicle and a woman attacked them.
And those surrounding them attempted to run them over and ram them with her vehicle.
An officer of ours acted quickly and defensively shot to protect himself and the people around him.
And I don't have to say this, but for the record, none of that is true.
And it is wholly and completely false.
The mayor said, ICE, get the F out of our city.
And people are responding to me saying, oh, they love to talk.
Saying, well, what would you do then?
And that, that is why these people have been able to expand and advance their tyranny.
Because people like that are in numerous numbers.
People who say, well, what would you do then?
Instead of saying, what are they doing other than talking?
For the record, what I would do is have the police force arrest ICE.
Yeah, what I would do is have the emergency meeting with my city council to figure out how we can create impediments for ICE.
Call it the third eye initiative.
Immediate implementation of impediments.
What I would do is coalition build with the organizations who are already filling the gaps that bureaucracy has created and organize forums so that we can get our constituency informed on how they can fight back.
What I would do is understand wholeheartedly that I, as a mayor, am dealing with a fascist government that is no longer operating lawfully or even under the guise of lawfully.
And thus, my town needs to be doing everything in its power to be sovereign.
Go look into abolitionist history.
Take a look at the town of Christiana, Pennsylvania's response to the Fugitive Slave Act.
Take a look at Syracuse, New York's response to the Fugitive Slave Act in the 1850s.
If you don't feel that your elected officials, whose literal careers are based on your dollars, should be expected to go to any lengths to protect you, then you've already given up.